BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12)
1946-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/012
5.5 cubic feet
5.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective labor agreements.
5833682
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 05, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 21, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) was established in 1884 to collect information about employment and labor in the United States. As mandated by the 1947 Taft-Hartley Act, the BLS was formally tasked with responsibility for soliciting, collecting, and analyzing collective bargaining agreements (CBAs) from public and private establishments, and making the agreements publicly available. In the early 1980s, this was function was limited to union contracts made with employers of 1000 or more employees.
In 2002, the National Archives and Records Administration authorized the BLS to donate inactive, non-confidential agreements which were 5 years or more past their expiration date to the Kheel Center where they would be preserved and made available to the public. The Office of Labor-Management Services took over responsibility for collecting and analyzing CBAs in 2011, and continues this donor relationship with the Kheel Center.
Scope and Contents
The US Department of Labor Historical Collective Bargaining Agreements Collection, 6178, is made up of 21 series of expired public- and private-sector collective bargaining agreements dating from 1887 to 2003 and totals 685 linear feet plus 10 CDs of digitized documents and 320 reels of microfilm. In addition to the CBAs, a small volume of related documents such as union constitutions, pension and health plans submitted to the BLS, are also available.
Selected collective bargaining agreements from this collection were digitized with generous funding from the National Historic Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC), and the National Science Foundation (NSF). Because documents other than collective bargaining agreements were also collected and preserved here by the US Department of Labor, a folder containing material that has been digitized, may also contain material which has not been digitized such as constitutions, bylaws, working rules, life insurance plans, or other organizational documents. For access to non-digitized material, contact Kheel Center staff.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Arrangement
Series I: Industry Code #11, Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing and Hunting
Series II: Industry Code #21, Mining, Quarrying, and Oil and Gas Extraction
Series III: Industry Code #22, Utilities
Series IV: Industry Code #23, Construction
Series V: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
Series VI: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
Series VII: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
Series VIII: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade
Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
Series X: Industry Code #45, Retail Trade
Series XI: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
Series XII: Industry Code #49, Transportation and Warehousing
Series XIII: Industry Code #51, Information
Series XIV: Industry Code #52, Finance and Insurance
Series XV: Industry Code #54, Professional, Scientific, and Technical Services
Series XVI: Industry Code #56, Administrative and Support and Waste Management and Remediation Services
Series XVII: Code #62, Health Care and Social Assistance
Series XVIII: Code #71, Arts, Entertainment, and Recreation
Series XIX: Code #72, Accommodation and Food Services
Series XX: Code #81, Other Services (except Public Administration)
Industrial relations -- United States; Collective labor agreements - United States.; United States. Department of Labor -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Division of Industrial Relations -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Office of Wages and Industrial Relations --Archives
5833682
- Series I: Industry Code #11, Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing and Hunting
  - Code no.560916: Liggett and Myers Tobacco Co. and Tobacco Workers' International Union, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Code no.550586: Commercial Fishing, San Diego, California and Cannery Workers and Fishermen's Union of San Diego, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Series II: Industry Code #21, Mining, Quarrying, and Oil and Gas Extraction
  - Code no.561603: Calvert City Chemical Company and United Mine Workers of America District 50, Local 13951, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Code no.570687: Carbon Limestone Company and United Mine Workers of America, Local 14712, International Union of District 50, 1965- 1968 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Code no.560674: Collier Companies and National Maritime Union of America, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Series III: Industry Code #22, Utilities
  - Code no.570672: Hackensack Water Company and Utility Workers Union of America, Local 375, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Code no.541686: North Electric Company of Galion, Ohio and Independent Worker's Union of North Electric Company, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Code no.560377: Public Service Electric and Gas Company and Camden Coke and Gas Works Independent Federation, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Code no.560623: Central Hudson Gas and Electric Corporation and Central Hudson Employees Association, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Code no.561784: Nebraska Power Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1483, 1946-1965 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Code no.552093: Illinois Power Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Locals 309,702, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Code no.570692: General Telephone Company of the Southeast and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2035, 1967- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Code no.571132: Public Service Electric and Gas Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Locals 2060, 2178, 1967- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Code no.571133: Public Service Electric and Gas Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2060, 1967- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Code no.570760: Rio Grande Valley Gas Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 4-604, 1964- 1967 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Code no.580044: Gas Service Company and International Union of District 50, United Mine Workers of America, Local 12329, 1967- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Series IV: Industry Code #23, Construction
  - Code no.530637: Shaft and Tunnel Work Companies and International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union, Local 17, 1962- 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Code no.541007: General Cleaning Contractors Association of Seattle and Building Service Employees International Union, Local 6, 1963- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Code no.550117: Millwright, Conveyor and Machine Erector Contractors and Millwrights Local 1102, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Code no.551230: General Contractors Association of Louisville, Inc. and Falls City Carpenters District Council and its Affiliated Unions, 1965- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Code no.551231: General Contractors Association of Louisville, Inc. and General Drivers, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Local 89, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Code no.551633: Dade and Monroe Counties Plumbing Contractors and Plumbers Local Union 519 of Miami, Florida, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Code no.551789: Associated Building Contractors of Fort Wayne, Indiana and International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers Union of America, District Council 57, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Code no.551993: Painting and Decorating Contractors of America and Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, Local 86, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Code no.560929: Associated Builders and Contractors of Fairfield County, Inc. and Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers Union, Local 8, 1966- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Code no.561416: General Contractors Association of Louisville, Inc. and Hod Carriers Union, Local 86, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Code no.561894: Associated General Contractors of America and Laborers International Union of North America, Local 1410, 1966- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Code no.570058: Madway Main Line Homes, Inc. - Portable Unit Division and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America - Metropolitan District Council, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Code no.571035: Mason Contractors Association of Indiana, Inc. and Bricklayers Union, Local 6, 1966-1972 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Code no.540914: Labor Negotiating Committee of Ready-Mixed Concrete Industry and Construction Laborers and Material Handlers, Local 1058, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Code no.541170: South Du Page County Mason Contractors' Assoc. and Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers Union, Local 74, 1964- 1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Code no.541201: Associated General Contractors of America, Houston Chapter and Pile Drivers, Bridge, Dock and Wharf Builders, of Carpenters Local 526, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Code no.560932: Tampa Master Plumbing and Heating Dealers Association and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry of the United States and Canada, Local 624, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Code no.571066: Will County Contractors Association and Carpenters District Council of Will County and Vicinity, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Code no.550959: Carpet, Linoleum and Resilient Floors Industry Employers and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 2265, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Code no.551034: Air Conditioning, Refrigeration, Heating and Piping Association and United Association, Local 725 of Miami, Florida, 1965- 1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Code no.551228: Quincy Master Builders Association and Quincy Carpenters Local 762, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Code no.552011: Carpenters District Council of Houston and Vicinity and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 2265, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Code no.560278: Fort Smith Contractors Association and International Hod Carriers' Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, Local 107, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Code no.560837: Minot, North Dakota Construction Companies and Bricklayers Local Union 2, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Code no.561128: Gas and Pipe Line Construction Employers and Hod Carriers Union, District Council of Washington, D.C., 1963- 1966 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Code no.561474: Building Trades Employers' Association and International Union of Operating Engineers, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Code no.590966: Associated General Contractors of Minnesota, Minneapolis and St. Paul Builders Divisions and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 49, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Code no.561004: Building Contractors of Colorado, Inc. and Laborers International Union of North America, Local 398, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Code no.561339: Associated General Contractors of America, Detroit Chapter and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Locals 247, 614, 339, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Code no.561839: Construction Contractors in Colorado and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 135, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Code no.570992: Home Builders Association of Palm Beach County, Inc. and Palm Beach County Carpenters District Council, 1966- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Code no.570393: Long Island Builders Institute, Inc. and General Building Laborers' Local 66, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Code no.570488: Madison Employers Council and Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers International Union, Local 13, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Code no.570735: Building Trades Employers' Association of Westchester and Putnam Counties and Teamsters and Chauffeurs Union, Local 456, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Code no.570838: Associated General Contractors of America, Oregon-Columbia Chapter and Hoisting and Portable Engineers, Local 701 of the International Union of Operating Engineers, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Code no.570964: North Plains Contractors Association and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 1201, 1967- 1970 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Code no.580029: Associated General Contractors, Akron Chapter and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 18, 18A, 18B, 1967- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Series V: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
  - Code no.550496: Irving Air Chute Co., Inc. and United Textile Workers of America Local 277, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Code no.550823: David Davies, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 346, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Code no.551030: Cherryvale Manufacturing Company, Inc. and United Garment Workers of America, Local 413, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Code no.551286: Oscar Mayer and Company, Inc. and Beef Boners and Sausage Makers Local Union No. 100, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Code no.551370: Hygrade Food Products Corporation and Sausage Makers' Union Local 203, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Code no.551550: G. Levor and Co., Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 41L, 1965- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Code no.552035: Colonial Baking Company and Bakers Local Union 305 of Jackson, Mississippi, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Code no.561127: Stegmaier Brewing Company and Brewery and Soft Drink Workers Union, Local 163, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Code no.561226: Dairy Employers' Labor Council and Dairy and Creamery Workers Union, Local 951, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Code no.561550: Sayles Biltmore Bleacheries and United Textile Workers of America, Local 2589, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Code no.561676: Mohawk Drapery Manufacturing Co. and United Textile Workers of America, Local 206, 1966-1966 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Code no.570409: Dawson's Brewery, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 59, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Code no.570717: American Sugar Company and United Packinghouse Food and Allied Workers, Local 1101, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Code no.571122: Libby, McNeill and Libby and Food Processors, Drivers and Helpers, Local 809, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Code no.580053: Omar Bakeries, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 413, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Code no.541179: Levi Strauss, Co. and International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Code no.550600: N. Margolin and Company, Inc. and Joint Board of New England of the International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers' Union, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Code no.551517: Footprints, Inc. and United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council 10, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Code no.552227: National Sugar Manufacturing Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Local 275, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Code no.560729: Strong, Hewat and Co., Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Code no.561169: Beco Products Corporation and Warehouse and Mail Order Employees Union, Local 743, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Code no.561530: C. Schmidt and Sons, Inc. and International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, Local 164, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Code no.561573: Durham Hosiery Mills and American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Code no.540956: California Packing Corporation and Packing House Employees and Warehousemen, Locals 616,629,698, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Code no.550803: United Biscuit Company of America, Melrose Park Bakery and American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 1, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Code no.550925: Awning Companies of Detroit and Awning Display Decorator's and Metal Fabricator Union, Local 877, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Code no.551081: Texas Textile Mills, Inc. and United Textile Workers of America, Local 515, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Code no.551127: Brewing Companies of Hartford and Brewery Workers, Local 35 of Hartford, Connecticut, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Code no.551656: Puritan Mills, Inc. and Upper South Department of the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Code no.551854: Oxford Textile Finishing Co. and Textile Workers Union of America, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Code no.552013: Continental Manufacturing Company and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Code no.552111: French Worsted Company and Industrial Trades Union of America, French Worsted Local, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Code no.552290: Jewel Cotton Mills, Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Code no.560581: Monterey Fish Processors Association and Fish Cannery Workers Union of the Pacific, AFL, 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Code no.560594: Hoosac Mills Corp. and Northern Berkshire Executive Textile Council, 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Code no.560920: Maplewood Yarn Mills, Inc. and Textile Workers' Union of America, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Code no.560925: Newburgh-Middletown-Poughkeepsie Area Bakery Operators Group and American Bakery and Confectionery Workers Union, Local 50, 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Code no.561001: Beaunit Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, Local 76, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Code no.551066: Block Cut Manufacturers, Inc. and Consolidated Glove Cutters and Shavers Union, Local 1714, 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Code no.561027: Associated Garment Industries of St. Louis and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, St. Louis Joint Board of, 1966- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Code no.561110: Pepperell Manufacturing Company, Lewiston, Maine and Textile Workers Union of America-CLC, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Code no.561203: Arms Textile Manufacturing Co., Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Code no.561600: Baltic Mills Company and United Textile Workers of America, Local 45, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Code no.561824: Newark Area Bakery Employers Labor Council and Bakery Drivers and Salesman, Local 194, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Code no.580003: Fulton County Glove Manufacturers, Inc. and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Local 292 - Glove Cities Area Joint Board, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Code no.580002: Fulton County Glove Manufacturers, Inc. and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Local 292, Glove Cities Area Joint Board (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Code no.580192: Block Cut Manufacturers, Inc. and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Layers-Off Union Local 292, Glove Cities Area Joint Board, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Code no.580193: Block Cut Manufacturers, Inc. and United Glove Workers of America, Operators and Day Hands Branch, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Code no.541119: International Shoe Company, St. Louis, Missouri and District 50, United Mine Workers of America, Local 12961, 1964- 1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Code no.551004: Standard Cotton Products, Co. and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers, Local 655, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Code no.552047: Customs and Reupholstering Shops of Chicago and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, Local 18, 1967- 1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Code no.570208: General Foods Corporation, Jell-O/Dover Operations and Amalgamated Food and Allied Workers, Local 56, 1966- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Code no.570394: Phillips-Van Heusen Corporation and United Garment Workers of America, Locals 283, 293, 343, 177, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Code no.570454: American Bakeries Company of Roanoke, Virginia and American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 503, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Code no.571247: Ralston Purina Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Local 110, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Code no.580209: Bigelow-Sanford, Inc. Carpet Company and Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1056, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Code no.590022: Bigelow-Sanford, Inc. Carpet Company and Watchmen and Guards Independent Union, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Series VI: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
  - Code no.551682: National Cash Register Company, Ithaca Supply Division Plant and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1607, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Code no.552153: Hamersley Manufacturing Company and United Papermakers and Paperworkers of America, Garfield Local 351, 1965- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Code no.560501: Employing Gravure Printers of New York City and Vicinity and New York Lithographers and Photo-Engravers' Union No. 1-P, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Code no.560768: Triangle Publications, Inc. and Bookbinders' and Bindery Women's Union, Local 2, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Code no.560869: National Blank Book Company and International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, Local 48, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Code no.561026: Allied Chemical Corporation, Barrett Division and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 660, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Code no.561436: Vi-Den Products Co., Inc. and Woodworkers and Mechanics Union of Weston, WV, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Code no.561545: Standard Oil Company and Petroleum Workers Local Union, Local 10, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Code no.570222: Indiana Limestone Institute and Journeymen Stone Cutters Association, Bedford Local Union, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 60)